<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jolande Poel</title>
    <link>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jolande Poel</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Jolande Poel</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
<<<<<<< HEAD
      <title>Data Science Specialist training</title>
      <link>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/ds-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/ds-specialist/</guid>
      <description>Data Science Specialist course completeWith the help of ITvitae Learning in Amersfoort, I successfully completed my Data Science Specialist course. We started 16 January 2017 and finished on 3 June 2017. It’s now named Data Science Professional and the subjects have changed a bit. The subjects I had were:
Introduction Statistics and Data Analysis taught by Wobbe ZijlstraProgramming in R taught by Wobbe Zijlstra and Hicham ZmarrouGraphical Analysis taught by Edwin de JongeStatistical Learning taught by Wobbe ZijlstraMachine Learning taught by Hicham ZmarrouText Analysis taught by Mark van der LooTime series and Trend Analysis taught by Jan van der LaanWorking with Big Data taught by Bas van ZelstIntroduction to Statistics and Data AnalysisIn this 6-day course spread over 3 weeks we learned the basics of statistics including mean, median, mode, ANOVA and basic graphs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first post</title>
      <link>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Jolande and I just succesfully made this site. Finally. After having a run-in with git submodules. Again.
I wanted to try out some R code to see if this all works correctly:
data(&amp;quot;iris&amp;quot;)library(tidyverse)## -- Attaching packages ----------------------------------------------- tidyverse 1.2.1 --## v ggplot2 2.2.1 v purrr 0.2.4## v tibble 1.4.2 v dplyr 0.7.4## v tidyr 0.8.0 v stringr 1.2.0## v readr 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
=======
>>>>>>> parent of 892f710... Build site 2018-02-21
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic is a framework to help you create a beautiful website quickly. Perfect for personal sites, blogs, or business/project sites. Check out the latest demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes. Then head on over to the Quick Start guide or take a look at the Release Notes.

Key features:
 Easily manage various content including homepage, blog posts, publications, talks, and projects Extensible via color themes and widgets/plugins Write in Markdown for easy formatting and code highlighting, with LaTeX for mathematical expressions Social/academic network linking, Google Analytics, and Disqus comments Responsive and mobile friendly Simple and refreshing one page design Multilingual and easy to customize  Color Themes Academic is available in different color themes and font themes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jolandepoel.github.io/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>